weblinkconnect.com 2015-06-07

# WebLink Privacy Policy

### Your Privacy is Important to Us

Our privacy policy, as detailed below, answers questions you may have about access, security and control of personal information. It also describes how the information will be used and whether it will be provided to third parties.

At WebLink International, we believe that your personal information including your name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card data belongs to you. While we collect this type of information when you provide it to us, we do not rent or sell it to third parties. We use it only to process orders and to provide a more personalized experience.

### What information does WebLink collect?

When users visit our Website, there are two types of information that may be collected.

The first type of information is known as “personally identifiable information.” In order to serve your needs and to provide improved products and services, we may from time to time request personal and private information, such as your name or company, address, contact information, interests, payment information when you place orders, survey information and/or other information. You may choose to provide this information at your option. Many areas of our site are accessible without providing any personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information excludes any information you may choose to submit publicly, such as reviews, critiques, editorials, testimonials, documentaries, forum or blog discussions.

If you place an order, certain private information will be needed, such as your name or company, address, contact information and payment arrangements. We will maintain a history of orders and payments via your account for normal accounting and business purposes. WebLink International, does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or companies that are not our partners.

If you choose not to provide private information to this Web site, alternate ordering and payment arrangements can be made by providing the necessary information via telephone, fax or mail, or via another standard method of communication.

We may use your e-mail address to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Website, new services and special offers we think you’ll find valuable. If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt out by emailing us at 3partyoptout@weblinkinternational.com stating your request at  and so specifying. This opt out does not apply to information exchanged via email to facilitate, complete or confirm our transaction with you, to provide warranty or security information, to notify you of a change in terms or features, or to deliver to you goods or services, including updates or upgrades, that you are entitled to receive.

We may release account information when we believe, in good faith that such release is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with law, (2) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or (3) protect the rights, property or safety of WebLink International and its partners, our users or others.

We may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to:

  * respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; or defend against legal claims.
  * believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of WebLink International’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * transfer information about you if WebLink International is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, WebLink International will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

The second type of information is known as “non-personally identifiable information” and is collected upon each visit to our Website. Our server automatically recognizes visitors’ domain names and Internet Protocol addresses (where possible). We also collect information and statistics about how visitors use the site. This information, which is collected and maintained in an anonymous, non-personal and composite form, allows us to improve the content of our Website and facilitate market research.

### Does WebLink use non-personally identifiable information?

On occasion, we may provide non-personally identifiable information about our users, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors to help us understand this information better. However, these statistics will not include any personally identifiable information. Other than improving our Website and providing our visitors with the best experience possible, we make no other use of this information.

### Does WebLink use non-personally identifiable information?

On occasion, we may provide non-personally identifiable information about our users, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors to help us understand this information better. However, these statistics will not include any personally identifiable information. Other than improving our Website and providing our visitors with the best experience possible, we make no other use of this information.

### Cookies

When you visit a Website, information may be stored in a file known as a “cookie.” This file is stored on your computer and is used for future reference. If you revisit a Website, the cookie allows that Website to identify you as a returning guest and tailor your shopping experience to you.

We use cookies in two places. The first is when a user fills out a form on our site. We use cookies to fill in their name and e-mail address in the form where appropriate (this is known as “auto-fill.”) The second is when a customer uses the Contact Us page or another landing page. Again, we use cookies for auto-filling the form.

Most web browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your web browser’s help file to learn more about these functions.

The information contained in our cookies is only used by WebLink International. Your web browser will not pass a cookie to a site other than the one that created it.

### Security

WebLink is committed to maintaining the privacy of your personally identifiable information, and will treat the privacy of your information with the same or greater security protections as we provide for our own private information. WebLink International company Websites have industry-standard security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet, we take reasonable steps to ensure the safety of all information. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up to date on our security and privacy practices.

### Your Consent and Notification of Changes

By using this Website, products and services, you consent to the terms of this policy. If our privacy policy changes, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of access, security, control of personal information, how information will be used, and whether it will be provided to third parties. Your continued use of the Website constitutes your consent to the updated policy.

### Do Not Call Policy

WebLink International strives to maintain the highest standards of ethical conduct in its marketing activities and is committed to complying with all federal and state legislation.

No employee or agent of WebLink International shall engage in telemarketing practices that violate the terms of the Telephone Consumer Protection Act of 1991, the FTC Telephone Sales Rule or state regulations.

If you do not want to receive sales calls from WebLink International, you may request to have your name placed on our Do Not Call List. We will process your request and remove your name from our active list within 10 days. You can make this request by email or mail as follows:

Email us at donotcall@weblinkinternational.com, or mail to WebLink International, Attn: Do Not Call List, 3905 W. Vincennes Road, Suite 210 Indianapolis, IN 46268

When submitting a request, be sure to include all the relevant information that you want added to our Do Not Call List, i.e., full name, address, and telephone number(s). Subsequent sign-ups or inquiries may lead to new record creations; these actions by you may lead to inadvertent contact. If that is the case, please do not hesitate to contact us to reiterate the Do Not Call requests. If your information changes, please notify us of your new name, address, and telephone number(s) so that you will remain on the Do Not Call List.

If you would like us to remove you from our Do Not Call List so that you may receive our telephone solicitations, notify us by contacting Customer Support at support@weblinkinternational.com.

Being on the WebLink International’s Do Not Call List restricts telephone offers for sales only. We may still call you about service and fulfillment issues, surveys, billing and other topics.

_–Revised September 23, 2014_
